(Bernadette:)I love
that you have the confidence
(Bernadette:)to speak, even without giving it
an ounce of thought.
(Howard:)And I love how your hair
is always on the soap.
(Howard:)It's like washing myself
with a hamster.
(knocking on door)
(Raj:)Hey, guys.
Sorry I am so late.
(Raj:)I was on the phone
with my mother.
(Bernadette:)Oh, how is she?
(Raj:)Pretty good.
(Raj:)She bought the book
Eat, Pray, Love
(Raj:)and used it to set my father's
Mercedes on fire.
(Raj:)So, what's up with you guys?
(Howard:)We're just saying all the things
we love about each other.
(Raj:)Oh, like you and I
did at couples therapy.
Ooh, what'd you get?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I ordered it
before your surgery.
(Sheldon:)It's the urn I was going
to put you in.
(Penny:)Okay, that's morbid.
(Penny:)Send it back.
(Sheldon:)I can't send it back--
I had it engraved.
"Here lie the ashes
of Leonard Hofstadter.
(Sheldon:)He thought he was right,
but his roommate knew better."
(Leonard:)That's funny.
(Leonard:)Boy, I'm gonna miss
these painkillers.
(Penny:)Hey, why did you get two?
"I'm with stupid."
Oh, that one's mine.